dotcomwebdesign.com 2011-04-24

# Dotcomwebdesign.com - Web Design Sydney Australia - Free Website Templates, Quality, Affordable & Cheap Webdesign - Privacy Policy

**_Dotcomwebdesign is a provider of free website templates only and as such we  accept no responsibility for any content placed on of any of the websites that have chosen to use our templates._**

If you require more information or maybe you have some questions about our privacy policy, please do feel free to contact us by email at [privacy@dotcomwebdesign.com](mailto:privacy@dotcomwebdesign.com)

At [http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com/), the privacy of our visitors is very important. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by [http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com/) and how it is used. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, [http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocols ( IP ) addresses, types of browsers, Internet Service Providers ( ISP's ), date/time stamps, referring/exit pages, and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer our site, track user’s movement around our site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

[http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense & Bidvertiser. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on dotcomwebdesign.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content [network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology for their advertisements and links that appear on [http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com/) that are sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

[http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com/) has no access to/or control these cookies that are used by these third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. [http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com's](http://www.dotcomwebdesign.com%27s/) privacy policy does not apply to, and we can't control the activities of such advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable your cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
